リリースビルド時にはSampleフォルダ以下を丸ごと削除するか、Editorフォルダ以下に置くようにしてください。
Unityでは、Resoucesフォルダ以下にあるアセットは、自動的にアプリに含まれてしまいます。
サンプルにはResoucesフォルダ以下にたくさんの素材がありますので、削除などをしないとアプリサイズの肥大化の原因になります。


Or at the time of release build to whole delete the Sample folder below, so please put the Editor folder below.
In Unity, assets in the following Resouces folder, will be automatically included in the app.
Since there is a lot of material in the following Resouces folder in the sample, it will cause a bloated app size If you do not or delete.